<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City</string>
    <string name="goodtaste_title">Good Taste</string>
    <string name="goodtaste_description">Nestled in the heart of Baguio, GoodTaste Restaurant is a Filipino-style establishment that offers delicious and affordable comfort food. The ambiance is lively and bustling, perfect for large groups and families. The interior design is simple yet functional, with long tables that can accommodate big parties. The price range is very reasonable, making it an ideal place for budget-conscious diners.</string>
    <string name="goodtaste_address">Otek Street, Baguio City</string>
    <string name="farmerdaughter_title">Farmer\'s Daughter</string>
    <string name="farmerdaughter_description">The Farmer’s Daughter is housed in a structure with an architecture inspired by a traditional Igorot (a Filipino ethnic group in the Cordilleras) house, as you can see in the photo above. It has wooden interior and furnitures, giving a homey and rustic vibe.</string>
    <string name="farmerdaughter_address">Tam-awan Village</string>
    <string name="oh_my_gulay_title">Oh My Gulay</string>
    <string name="oh_my_gulay_description">Oh My Gulay Baguio, the creative restaurant at the top of La Azotea Building can certainly be considered a Baguio classic. Before the pandemic and the social media boom, Oh My Gulay has been providing flavorful vegetarian dishes. </string>
    <string name="oh_my_gulay_address">La Azotea Building along Session Road</string>
    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins_title">Cafe By The Ruins</string>
    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins_description">If you’re looking for a cozy spot in Baguio where you can take a sip of Tsokolate, then Café by the Ruins is ideal for that experience. This place is well-known by both locals and tourists and offers natural and local ingredients of the region. They also offer vegetarian options in their menu. </string>
    <string name="cafe_by_the_ruins_address">25 Shuntug Rd. Baguio City</string>
    <string name="hardin_title">Hardin</string>
    <string name="hardin_description">Hardin is a favorite restobar–slash-cafe among locals and tourists alike for its great atmosphere and even greater food. It is a great place to chill and drink, with usually live bands singing. Drinks are reasonably priced at 80-150php for beers, 250-300php for cocktail pitchers. The people drinking here are usually adults but there is always something happening at Hardin so it\'s never boring!</string>
    <string name="hardin_address">Leonard Wood Road</string>
    <string name="alberto_title">Alberto\'s Bar</string>
    <string name="alberto_description">Alberto\'s Bar is a popular spot among locals in Baguio, offering a vibrant atmosphere and live music that ranges from beloved American country tunes to traditional Cordilleran melodies. The bar exudes a fantastic vibe, with talented performers and a wide selection of drinks and food.</string>
    <string name="alberto_address">Dr Carino St. Baguio City</string>
    <string name="burnham_title">Burnham Park</string>
    <string name="burnham_description">The park is named after Daniel Hudson Burnham, an American architect and urban planner. He was also the one who laid the plans and design for Baguio City. Most of the park’s features were originally from Daniel Burnham’s design but a few changes and alterations were made to enhance the park’s beauty.</string>
    <string name="burnham_address">Lake Drive Baguio City</string>
    <string name="wright_title">Wright Park</string>
    <string name="wright_description">Wright Park Baguio was named after Governor Luke E. Wright, who ordered architect Daniel Burnham to design the park. The park is located in the central part of Baguio City near the Mansion.</string>
    <string name="wright_address">Near Pacdal</string>
    <string name="baguio_night_market_title">Baguio City Night Market</string>
    <string name="baguio_night_market_description">From 9 PM onwards, the street transforms into a vibrant marketplace filled with stalls offering a wide array of goods from thrift stores and handcrafted souvenirs to toys and household items all at incredibly low prices.</string>
    <string name="baguio_night_market_address">Along Harrison Road</string>
    <string name="good_shepherd_convent_title">Good Shepherd Convent</string>
    <string name="good_shepherd_convent_description">Home to the Mountain Maid brand, a wide range of sweet delights like purple yam jam, peanut brittle, and homemade breads, Good Shepherd Convent is run by nuns who originally whipped up these delectable treats to primarily help feed the needy.</string>
    <string name="good_shepherd_convent_address">88 Gibraltar Rd, Baguio, Benguet</string>
    <string name="city_market_title">Baguio City Market</string>
    <string name="city_market_description">Baguio City Market is the ‘melting pot’ of the Cordillera and lowland products. While it may be busy at times, a day spent in the market is not at all stressful. It offers a wide range of products as well as services.</string>
    <string name="city_market_address">Magsaysay Ave.</string>
    <string name="camp_john_hay_title">Camp John Hay</string>
    <string name="camp_john_hay_description"> Camp John Hay dates back to the early 1900s when it was established as a military base for the United States Armed Forces. It was named after John Milton Hay, the US Secretary of State under Presidents William McKinley and Theodore Roosevelt.</string>
    <string name="camp_john_hay_address">Camp John Hay Baguio City</string>
    <string name="mines_view_title">Mines View Park</string>
    <string name="mines_view_description">Mines View Park is one of the most popular tourist spots in Baguio City. Located just a few minutes from the city center, this park offers stunning views of the mountains and the mines that give it its name.</string>
    <string name="mines_view_address">Pacdal Baguio City</string>
    <string name="mount_costa_title">Mount Costa</string>
    <string name="mount_costa_description">Mount Costa is the outdoor living room everybody dreams to have. With its collection of 24 gardens inspired by the world’s best gardens, Mount Costa is one of the newest attractions near the city of Baguio.</string>
    <string name="mount_costa_address">Upper Lamtang, Puguis, La Trinidad, Benguet</string>
    <string name="the_mansion_title">The Mansion</string>
    <string name="the_mansion_description">The Mansion in Baguio City, built in 1908 as the summer residence for U.S. Governors-General.</string>
    <string name="the_mansion_address">Pacdal Baguio City</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="bars_category">Bars</string>
    <string name="parks_category">Parks</string>
    <string name="shops_category">Shops</string>
    <string name="attractions_category">Other Attractions</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="baguio_city_title">Baguio City</string>
    <string name="baguio_city_description">Baguio City, Hailed as the Summer Capital of the Philippines, Baguio is the top destination to go to if you want to take a break from the tropical heat in the lowlands. With average temperatures ranging from 15-23°C, the city rarely experiences temperatures higher than 26°C even during the warmest parts of the year. Because of this climate, Baguio is also home to beautiful plants that wouldn’t usually survive elsewhere in the county. Also nicknamed the City of Pines, you’ll be in for a treat with all the beautiful flowers and lush vegetation as you enter the vicinity. It will truly feel as if you’re entering a different world.</string>
</resources>